joomlancers.com 2018-06-30

# JOOMLANCERS.COM PRIVACY POLICY

THE AFOREMENTIONED IS THE PRIVACY POLICY THAT GOVERNS YOUR USE OF ANY JOOMLANCERS' SERVICE.

This Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy") applies to Joomlancers.com 

At Joomlancers.com, we recognize the privacy needs of our Customers. You should be able to choose what information you want to share and decide what will happen to that information once it has been shared. Protecting your personal information is vitally important. Please read the following Privacy Policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of our many offerings. This policy may change from time to time without notice so please check back periodically. We hope this will increase your awareness about online privacy. 

** Collected Information  **   
If you choose to use and or purchase a Joomlancers.com product or place an order with us, we may ask you to provide us with certain personal information, such as your name, physical and electronic mail ("e-mail") addresses, phone number, domain name and other information that by itself, or in combination with other information, may be identifiable to you as a specific individual. We may also ask for financial information, such as account or credit card numbers, and demographic information, such as your zip code. 

**Disclosure**   
**Joomlancers.com will not sell, rent, trade, or disclose individual Customer information to any third parties or outside companies** who will use the information to contact you or who will share the information with others without your permission. It may be necessary to disclose information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing the information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating Joomlancers.com's policies or may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) the rights or property of Joomlancers.com, other Joomlancers.com users, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. Joomlancers.com may disclose or access account information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it or for administrative and other purposes that we deem necessary to maintain, service, and improve our products and Services. 

** Use of Information  **   
The use of an individual's e-mail address is necessary to keep our Customers well informed of maintenance issues, escalated critical issues and problem resolutions that may arise with your Joomlancers.com Service. We may also use e-mail addresses to provide our Customers with informative newsletters. 

We like to keep our Customers informed via e-mail and other means. Sometimes Joomlancers.com uses personal and demographic information to help us determine which Joomlancers.com products and Services are most likely to be of interest to you or help diagnose problems with our servers or administration of our sites. We also use demographic information to gather general interest in our products, to help in the analysis of product usage, purchasing, and target markets. 

** Storage of Collected Information**

**Updated on 11th Nov 2010**  
The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card numbers) on our website, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). When Credit Card details are collected, we simply pass them on in order to be processed as required by secured third party gateway who is storing the data or looking after your data. We never permanently store complete Credit Card details. 

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. 

** Correct/Update  **   
If you want to change or modify information you have previously provided to us, please [ contact us ](http://www.joomlancers.com/explore/contact/ "Contact")

** Cookies  **   
Some of the websites we host place small bits of text or "cookies" onto your computer's hard drive. Cookies enable us to deliver content specific to your interests and keep track of your password so you do not have to re-enter it each time you visit our web sites. After you accept a cookie, it is passed from your browser to our servers each time you request a page. This cookie consists of a unique token that anonymously identifies to the server so that you can more easily access the features of the Joomlancers.com Service. Please note that you may configure your web browser to warn you before you accept a cookie. 

**Customer E-mails**   
** Joomlancers.com will not read or disclose e-mail content to others unless required by law or deemed necessary to operate our services.  **

** Contacting the Web Site    
** If you have any questions about Joomlancers.com's privacy policy or the privacy practices of our web sites, please [ contact us ](http://www.joomlancers.com/explore/contact/ "Contact") ****

**** Changes to the Privacy Policy  **   
In the event our Privacy Policy needs to be modified, those changes will be reflected in the next revision of this Privacy Policy which will be posted on the Joomlancers.com web site. Please check back often to review any revisions.   
**
